# Clarisa Díaz Bernasconi

Greater Valencia Metropolitan Area



clarisadb@gmail.com



657594212



linkedin.com/in/clarisadiazbernasconi

### Summary

Proactive, creative and with great capacity for work. I have been developing in the audiovisual field for more than 15 years and I am always looking to grow and find new challenges in this beautiful profession. I am an active person as a chief and I love working with large teams, I like to create a good environment where workers feel comfortable and achieve the required objectives.

### **Experience**



#### Editor / Chief Executive Officer

Gou videomarketing

Jan 2014 - Present (9 years 1 month)

### Post Production Editor

Gou videomarketing

Jan 2008 - Present (15 years 1 month)

Postproduction - Campaigns, Backstages, Storytelling, Youtube, Instagram and Facebook Ads

### Video Editor in Chief

**Buenos Aires City Government** 

Jan 2009 - Jan 2020 (11 years 1 month)

Management of a group of editors and post-producers who made institutional videos and published them in the media.

### **Editor - Post Production Coordinator**

Linead Camd S.A.

Jan 2008 - 2020 (12 years)

Post-production coordination in television campaigns (Government organizations and companies)

Tasks performed: Editing (Adobe Premiere and Final Cut) and post production coordination.

Preparation and monitoring of budgets

### **Post Production Coordinator**

Documental "Aventureros, soñadores, locos" for INCAA Instituto de Cine y Artes Audiovisuales

Jan 2011 - Dec 2011 (1 year)

From the pre-production of the 8 chapters of the documentary to post-production, I coordinated the work teams at all stages, meeting the delivery deadlines in a timely manner. Monitoring of the budget at each stage of production.

### Editor In Chief

#### Rincones de mi tierra

Mar 2007 - Feb 2008 (1 year)

Coordinate editors and post producers of documentary segments for TV and video in the Mexican tourism promotion production company "Rincones de mi Tierra". www.rinconesdemitierra.com Tasks performed: Editing and post-production in Final Cut.

## <sub>VIасом</sub> Т

#### Team Production (Mexico D.F.)

#### Viacom

Aug 2007 - Oct 2007 (3 months)

I was part of the production team in the broadcast of "Los Premios" of Mtv Latinamerica in 2007

### Media Production Coordinator

Acitron S.A.

Mar 2007 - May 2007 (3 months)

Post-production coordination in the final phase of the assembly of the documentary "Havanyork"

### Post Production Assistant

#### America TV

Jan 2007 - Mar 2007 (3 months)

Coordinación de postproducción y en el área de Videotape durante la transmisión de los segmentos en vivo.

#### Producer - Journalist

#### Greenpeace

Jun 2006 - Dec 2006 (7 months)

The first Tv Show for Greenpeace in Argentina host by Celebrities. Search and contact 13 Argentine Celebrities.

Coordination of outdoor recordings, arranging interviews for each report, search and selection of archive material, and coordination in the post-production of each program.

### Journalist - Content Producer

#### Canal 7 Argentina

Apr 2000 - Jul 2006 (6 years 4 months)

Production of guests, coordination of the journalistic team, Coordination of the live broadcast.

Production of special news reports, general interest and shows.

Coordination of the mobile unit outdoors.

### Producer

#### Canal A

Jan 1999 - Apr 2000 (1 year 4 months)

Production and realization of programs in the cultural channel "Canal a" for Álvarez y Asociados S.A. (currently "Tranquilo Producciones")

Completed tasks:

Arrangement and production of interviews with figures of Latin American culture. Search and selection of archive material, coordination of event recordings and live broadcasts. Among the outstanding cycles are: "Profiles, the faces of Latin America today...", International Independent Film Festival, Special Program for the University of Buenos Aires: "Why is Buenos Aires flooded", Special programs for the signal "I -Sat": "Jack the Ripper and "Freemasonry"

#### **Education**

Edit and Structure of the Story con Miguel Perez

2015 - 2015

♠ TEA

Journalist 2002 - 2005

Buenos Aires Comunicaciones

Tv And Film Director 1999 - 2000

#### **Skills**

After Effects • Adobe Premiere Pro • Content Marketing • Online Marketing • Social Media Marketing • English • Video Post-Production • Video Marketing • Team Leadership • Online Video Marketing